<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<items no="14">
<news id="1" date="09.26.2006 -" title="I just got a great gig at Ogilvy!" body="I&apos;ve always wanted to work for &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.ogilvy.com&quot;&gt;Ogilvy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;. This is a dream come true. Yeei!!!"></news>
<news id="2" date="10.02.2006 -" title="First day at Ogilvy" body="Although &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.ogilvy.com&quot;&gt;Ogilvy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; it&apos;s a great agency and the higher powers gave me the Associate Creative Director role, I didn&apos;t get the desired account. I was hoping to work on Cisco or American Express... I got Wyeth instead. I&apos;ve done pharma before but it&apos;s definitely not my cup o&apos; tea."></news>
<news id="3" date="11.20.2006 -" title="I'm already sick of this gig!" body="Over the years I&apos;ve met a whole slew of bizarre people at work that drove me out of my mind but never out of my job. Most consistently though I&apos;ve met very nice, diplomatic, highly organized, and very calm Producers/Project Managers. I thought these character traits are pretty much screened by HR when interviewing for new PMs. I just got a PM on my team that seems like a ferret on speed. Disorganized, spastic, and finger pointing. I have very conflicting emotions about him at this point: I&apos;m thinking to either kick him into sanity or just leave &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.ogilvy.com&quot;&gt;Ogilvy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; all together."></news>
<news id="4" date="01.05.2007 -" title="Wyeth's hormone replacement therapy line to go online" body="Happy New Year!... And what a beginning already! My current project is pharma. Listen to this: &quot;A salve for hot flashes suffered by menopausal women, Pristiq is a reuptake inhibitor now being studied with a specific focus on women. Initially it was developed for two indications that currently are pending approval from the FDA the treatment of major depressive disorder and vasomotor symptoms associated with menopause.&quot; Yikes!"></news>
<news id="5" date="02.27.2007 -" title="Informational need for women: Know Menopause" body="Just wrapped up my work on &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.knowmenopause.com&quot;&gt;Know Menopause&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; - a user-friendly site that provides useful, well-balanced information designed to help women better understand menopause and improve the interaction with their health care professionals. &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.knowmenopause.com&quot;&gt;Know Menopause&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; is a unique health educational tool sponsored by &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.wyeth.com&quot;&gt;Wyeth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; that enables women of menopausal age to learn about the changes they may experience during menopause and information about treatment options. An innovative blend of online resources and interactive tools, &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.knowmenopause.com&quot;&gt;Know Menopause&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; offers: videos with expert guidance from health care professionals, real-life patient stories, e-Cards to send to friends, women&apos;s wellness screener for health after age 40, an interactive menopausal symptoms assessor, and menopause treatment options."></news>
<news id="6" date="04.07.2007 -" title="I've just been appointed Ripple's new Creative Director" body="I&apos;m very excited about this opportunity but too busy with work to write up the news entry. I&apos;ll just quote the press release: &quot;Pittsburgh&apos;s largest online marketing firm, &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.r-effects.com&quot;&gt;Ripple Effects&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;, announced a senior-level hire for Creative Director recruited from a leading New York City agency. Alina joined &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.r-effects.com&quot;&gt;Ripple&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; from &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.ogilvy.com&quot;&gt;Ogilvy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;, a global leader in traditional and interactive marketing. As Creative Director, Alina will lead &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.r-effects.com&quot;&gt;Ripple&apos;s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; team of award-winning designers and developers, working in the newly remodeled Philadelphia office and in the Pittsburgh headquarters. Long term Alina will focus on establishing a New York office for &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.r-effects.com&quot;&gt;Ripple&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;.&quot;"></news>
<news id="7" date="04.14.2007 -" title="A few words about my new assignment" body="From &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.r-effects.com&quot;&gt;Ripple&apos;s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; President Paul Magnani, about apointing the Creative Director role: &quot;We spent six months on a national search for the Creative Director that would truly fit our culture, elevate our work for current clients, and broaden our customer base with new accounts. Alina will drive &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.r-effects.com&quot;&gt;Ripple&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; to expand further into viral marketing campaigns, cutting-edge use of interactive video and motion graphics, online social networking, and mobile phone marketing. With dozens of awards under her belt, fluency in multiple languages, and experience with leading both traditional and interactive fields, Alina is poised to elevate &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.r-effects.com&quot;&gt;Ripple&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; as a leader in online marketing.&quot;"></news>
<news id="8" date="05.08.2007 -" title="My first pitch won at Ripple: Wharton School of Business" body="This pitch was a piece of cake! The client was informed and super friendly. Not much to say about this assignment but maybe mention briefly that Wharton ranks consistently as one of the top institutions for business education in the world... Stand by for more news on this great project."></news>
<news id="9" date="05.19.2007 -" title="Web and mobile campaign launch for Bruster's Real Ice Cream" body="Today we launched &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.comeparfaitwithme.com&quot;&gt;Come Parfait With Me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;—a microsite to creatively extend Bruster&apos;s brand via its parfait product—and a mobile marketing initiative to increase traffic to participating retail locations. The &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.comeparfaitwithme.com&quot;&gt;microsite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; has several interactive elements including a game, to generate excitement about Bruster&apos;s in general, and its parfaits in particular. The recipients can redeem their forwarded text message coupons and also text in for bi-monthly offers."></news>
<news id="10" date="08.02.2007 -" title="Website launch for Tepper" body="The &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.tepper.cmu.edu/index.aspx&quot;&gt;Tepper School of Business&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; at &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.cmu.edu/index.shtml&quot;&gt;Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; unveiled a new website that projects a dynamic external face for the institution and underscores its leadership at the intersection of business and technology. Front and center are compelling stories about the &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.tepper.cmu.edu/index.aspx&quot;&gt;Tepper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; community and how the school continues to blaze new trails in business education, research, and practice worldwide. The website includes multimedia content covering the latest news and events, slideshows, audio and video podcasts, and interactive forums like enhanced message boards for program applicants."></news>
<news id="11" date="08.24.2007 -" title="Voice, text, video, rodents... Groundhog Crossing revamp!" body="Overwhelmed with the pressure that 96 out of 120 years the Shadow has been the cause of another six weeks of winter, the Shadow has fled Punxsutawney. Missing his lifelong friend, the Groundhog embarks on &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.groundhogcrossing.com&quot;&gt;Groundhog Crossing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;, a country-wide trek, to recover the Shadow and return to PA in time for Groundhog Day. While taking the driver&apos;s seat of a vehicle thousands of miles from PA, the user can zoom in on an interactive map, select video clips of Shadow-spottings across the country, sign up for email and text alerts, and leave mobile phone messages pleading for the Shadow&apos;s return."></news>
<news id="12" date="09.07.2007 -" title="I won a nice piece of business from Columbia University Medical Center" body="Having to interview quite a few doctors form the research team at &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://asp.cumc.columbia.edu/extrel/linksdisp.asp?year=2000&amp;selType=pressrel&quot;&gt;Columbia University Medical Center&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; for 2 solid months, the pitch work was assiduous. Yesterday however I aced the presentation and won the account. The subject of the project is chronic Lyme and will feature clinical research strategies aimed at developing new therapies, basic science to unravel the disease mechanisms and to identify better diagnostic tests, and education of both medical students and physicians on how to best evaluate and treat patients. "></news>
<news id="13" date="09.25.2007 -" title="Denim Highway relaunch" body="Lucky Brand Jeans needed help with expressing the excitement of the opening their new 45 retail locations accross the US. &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://denimhighway.nightagency.com&quot;&gt;Denim Highway&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt; is a cross-country tour in a renovated vintage bus, making stops at music festivals, roadside attractions, and store openings, while documenting the experience with blogs and videos at a psychedelic Americana-themed website."></news>
<news id="14" date="10.11.2007 -" title="Location change for Join The Movement" body="National Multiple Sclerosis Society has relocated &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.themsmovement.org&quot;&gt;Join The Movement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;. If you want to see the archived mark you have left, check out &lt;font color=&quot;#ff4f11&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.themsmovement.org/thewall.html&quot;&gt;The Wall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;. Help move us toward a world free of MS."></news>
</items>
